<resources>
    <string name="app_name">medical</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="home"> home</string>
    <string name="inquiry"> inquiry</string>
    <string name="shop"> shop</string>
    <string name="account">account</string>
    <string name="large_text">
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_health">health</string>
    <string name="shape_your_beard_like_a_pro_get_your_desired_beard_style_with_our_beardo_beard_shaping_styling_tool_and_get_the_best_beard_shape_at_home_its_design_makes_it_easy_to_form_perfect_lines_and_achieve_symmetry_combine_with_clippers_or_a_razor_to_achieve_an_accurate_trim_or_crisp_shave_this_smart_and_simple_tool_is_specifically_designed_to_give_you_a_good_beard_shape_you_get_a_multitude_of_shaping_choices_and_styling_options_adjust_the_curve_angle_and_use_different_levelling_measurements_to_try_something_new_even_shape_your_neckline_with_ease_learn_how_to_use_beard_shaping_tool_why_do_you_need_a_beard_shaping_tool_beardo_beard_shaping_tool_can_provide_the_best_styles_for_your_beard_adjust_the_tool_as_per_your_convenience_it_provides_a_symmetrical_edge_and_shape_to_your_face_you_can_adjust_the_angle_and_give_yourself_the_perfect_beard_look_level_your_measurements_for_trying_out_all_new_mustache_beard_styles_this_tool_gives_you_many_beard_styling_options_by_providing_options_to_style_your_neckline_easily"><![CDATA[Shape your Beard like a Pro! Get your desired beard style with our Beardo Beard Shaping & Styling Tool and get the best beard shape at home! Its design makes it easy to form perfect lines and achieve symmetry. Combine with clippers or a razor to achieve an accurate trim or crisp shave. This smart and simple tool is specifically designed to give you a good beard shape. You get a multitude of shaping choices and styling options. Adjust the curve angle and use different levelling measurements to try something new; even shape your neckline with ease! Learn how to use beard shaping tool Why do you need a Beard Shaping Tool? Beardo Beard Shaping Tool can provide the best styles for your beard. Adjust the tool as per your convenience. It provides a symmetrical edge and shape to your face. You can adjust the angle and give yourself the perfect beard look! Level your measurements for trying out all new mustache & beard styles. This tool gives you many beard styling options by providing options to style your neckline easily.]]></string>
    <string name="indulekha_bringha_oil_is_an_ayurvedic_medicine_to_prevent_hair_fall_and_promote_hair_growth_it_is_a_100_natural_ayurvedic_oil_that_has_been_clinically_proven_to_reduce_hair_fall_and_grows_new_hair_in_4_months_it_is_proven_on_real_male_and_female_consumers_having_mild_to_severe_hair_fall_it_is_enriched_with_bringharaj_a_herb_known_in_ayurveda_as_quot_keshraj_quot_also_known_as_king_of_hair_extracts_from_bringharaj_plants_are_known_for_their_medicinal_properties_that_not_only_reduce_hair_fall_but_also_revive_rejuvenate_the_process_of_hair_growth_the_extracts_of_the_herbs_are_cooked_in_virgin_coconut_oil_and_are_made_to_mature_under_natural_sunlight_for_7_days_the_power_of_the_sun_and_the_potency_of_these_herbs_goes_into_making_every_bottle_of_indulekha_oil_it_s_unique_and_easy_to_apply_straight_to_the_scalp_selfie_comb_allows_oil_to_penetrate_deep_inside_the_scalp_directly_without_getting_your_hands_oily_it_has_a_100_natural_fragrance_colour_and_is_recommended_by_ayurvedic_experts_for_people_suffering_from_hair_fall"><![CDATA[Indulekha Bringha Oil is an Ayurvedic medicine to prevent hair fall and promote hair growth. It is a 100% natural Ayurvedic oil that has been clinically proven to reduce hair fall and grows new hair in 4 months. It is proven on real male and female consumers having mild to severe hair fall. It is enriched with Bringharaj, a herb known in Ayurveda as \"Keshraj\", also known as King of Hair. Extracts from Bringharaj plants are known for their medicinal properties that not only reduce hair fall but also revive & rejuvenate the process of hair growth. The extracts of the herbs are cooked in virgin coconut oil and are made to mature under natural sunlight for 7 days. The power of the sun and the potency of these herbs goes into making every bottle of Indulekha Oil. It\'s unique and easy to apply straight to the scalp ‘selfie comb’ allows oil to penetrate deep inside the scalp directly, without getting your hands oily. It has a 100% natural fragrance, colour and is recommended by Ayurvedic experts for people suffering from hair fall.]]></string>
    <string name="dr_morepen_quit_out_is_a_non_sticky_mosquito_repellent_cream_that_provides_maximum_protection_from_deadly_mosquitoes_anytime_anywhere_its_unique_mosquito_repellent_formulation_is_used_to_provide_a_shield_from_pesky_disease_carriers_like_mosquitoes_it_acts_as_a_barrier_to_various_diseases_like_dengue_chikungunya_malaria_etc_it_helps_provide_skin_nourishment_with_vitamin_e_almond_oil_making_your_skin_healthy_and_safe_it_contains_no_harmful_chemicals_it_is_also_ideal_to_be_used_both_in_indoor_and_outdoor_locations"><![CDATA[Dr. Morepen Quit & Out is a non-sticky mosquito repellent cream that provides maximum protection from deadly mosquitoes anytime, anywhere. Its unique mosquito repellent formulation is used to provide a shield from pesky disease carriers like mosquitoes. It acts as a barrier to various diseases like Dengue, Chikungunya, Malaria, etc. It helps provide skin nourishment with Vitamin E & Almond Oil, making your skin healthy and safe. It contains no harmful chemicals. It is also ideal to be used both in indoor and outdoor locations.]]></string>
    <string name="soulflower_herbal_vitamin_c_under_eye_cream_with_rosehip_has_an_innovative_moisturising_formula_designed_specifically_for_the_delicate_skin_around_your_eyes_it_contains_natural_active_extracts_of_rosehip_oil_liquorice_that_reduce_the_appearance_of_dry_dehydrated_lines_and_vitamin_c_to_prevent_treat_ultraviolet_uv_induced_photodamage_in_addition_to_restoring_damage_caused_by_free_radicals_it_also_aids_in_collagen_synthesis_made_with_all_natural_ingredients_and_a_non_greasy_formulation_this_under_eye_cream_blends_seamlessly_into_the_skin"><![CDATA[Soulflower Herbal Vitamin C Under Eye Cream with Rosehip has an innovative moisturising formula designed specifically for the delicate skin around your eyes. It contains natural active extracts of rosehip oil & liquorice that reduce the appearance of dry & dehydrated lines and Vitamin C to prevent & treat ultraviolet (UV)-induced photodamage. In addition to restoring damage caused by free radicals, it also aids in collagen synthesis. Made with all-natural ingredients and a non-greasy formulation, this under-eye cream blends seamlessly into the skin.]]></string>
    <string name="himalaya_neem_and_turmeric_soap_blends_all_the_goodness_of_naturally_derived_ingredients_to_keep_your_skin_protected_at_all_times_the_himalaya_neem_turmeric_soap_cleanses_and_purifies_the_skin_the_powerful_oils_of_neem_and_turmeric_which_are_known_for_their_antibacterial_and_antifungal_properties_help_protect_your_skin_neem_is_an_excellent_skincare_ingredient_that_relieves_dry_skin_and_soothes_itchiness_redness_and_irritation_it_also_improves_general_skin_health_and_immunity_turmeric_has_strong_anti_inflammatory_properties_which_soothe_your_skin_gently_the_combination_of_these_potent_ingredients_in_this_himalaya_bathing_soap_is_good_to_start_your_day_refreshed_and_cleansed"><![CDATA[Himalaya Neem and Turmeric Soap blends all the goodness of naturally derived ingredients to keep your skin protected at all times. The Himalaya Neem & Turmeric Soap cleanses and purifies the skin. The powerful oils of Neem and Turmeric, which are known for their antibacterial and antifungal properties, help protect your skin. Neem is an excellent skincare ingredient that relieves dry skin and soothes itchiness, redness and irritation. It also improves general skin health and immunity. Turmeric has strong anti-inflammatory properties, which soothe your skin gently. The combination of these potent ingredients in this Himalaya Bathing Soap is good to start your day refreshed and cleansed.]]></string>
    <string name="beato_curv_mobile_glucometer_test_strips_come_with_a_complete_hygiene_check_and_are_packed_in_a_small_airtight_box_for_complete_protection_from_dust_bacteria_the_strips_are_of_premium_quality_and_instantly_draws_off_blood_when_the_pricked_finger_is_brought_near_the_strip_these_round_lancets_are_constructed_to_reduce_the_amount_of_pain_you_feel_while_pricking_yourself_and_provide_accurate_glucose_test_readings_the_tip_is_so_thin_that_you_will_hardly_feel_it_going_through_your_skin_only_a_tiny_prick_is_enough_to_draw_a_decent_amount_of_blood_key_features_of_beato_curv_strips_greater_shelf_life_easy_to_handle_very_flexible_tiny_blood_sample_0_6ul_key_features_of_round_lancets_designed_for_comfortable_glucose_testing_thinnest_needle_virtually_pain_free_testing_recommended_storage_tip_make_sure_to_keep_the_strips_away_from_direct_sunlight_or_rain_always_keep_them_in_a_cool_and_dry_area_the_ideal_temperature_for_storage_is_1_30_degree_celsius_do_not_freeze_these_strips_with_relatively_longer_shelf_life_these_sterile_lancets_can_be_stored_for_the_maximum_period"><![CDATA[BeatO CURV mobile Glucometer Test Strips come with a complete hygiene check and are packed in a small airtight box for complete protection from dust & bacteria. The strips are of premium quality and instantly draws off blood when the pricked finger is brought near the strip. These Round Lancets are constructed to reduce the amount of pain you feel while pricking yourself and provide accurate glucose test readings. The tip is so thin that you will hardly feel it going through your skin. Only a tiny prick is enough to draw a decent amount of blood. Key Features of BeatO CURV Strips - Greater shelf life - Easy to handle - Very flexible - Tiny blood sample (0.6uL) Key Features of Round Lancets - Designed for comfortable glucose testing - Thinnest needle - Virtually pain-free testing Recommended Storage Tip: Make sure to keep the strips away from direct sunlight or rain. Always keep them in a cool and dry area. The ideal temperature for storage is 1 – 30 Degree Celsius, do not freeze these strips. With relatively longer shelf life, these sterile lancets can be stored for the maximum period.]]></string>
</resources>